

ABOUT ME

Hi! I am Andrés, I am a visual artist and game developer. I have a Bachelor in Fine Arts (University of Seville), and a Master in Visual Game and Media Design (Royal Danish Academy, Copenhagen). For the last 5 years I have been working as a freelance artist and educator, I funded gamedev studio Goblin Rage (creator of BORE DOME), and I make all kinds of small interactive experiments. I love learning new tools and workflows, I am an avid problem-solver, and a great communicator. If left alone, I will most probably end up going on research rabbit holes about 3D print, energy systems, automation, or grow lights, among other things.

INFORMATION

Andrés Cabrero Rodríguez	z-Estecha		Andres_acre@hotmail.com			+45 81 94 02 61
Date of Birth: 05/04/1994 Nationality: Spain	<u> </u>	1	Artstation Page			Online Portfolio
EXPERIENCE						
10/2019 - (Today)			ame Engines (Unity, Unreal, Go lige Akademi (Copenhagen)	odot), Motion Capture	, VI	R, and Visual Design
03/2018 - (Today)	Freelance Illustrator (Gerda: A flame in winter - Porta Play 2022, The Tinderbox - Aviendo Aps 2019)					
14/12/20-31/12/20	3D artist and technical art for "The Game of Video Game Objects" for Jesper Juul					
03/2019 - 2023	Generalist Artist (3D, animation, technical art, shaders, concept) for BORE DOME (Goblin Rage)					
10/2017 - 01/2018	Animator and CG A	rtis	t for VR project at TimeStory -	VAT/CVR No.: 855536	i15	
PROJECTS						
12/2019 - 05/2022	PC game "BORE DOME" "Digital Moment" Award winner at A-MAZE 2022, Berlin. Role: Game Direction, 3D and Technical Art.					
10/18 - 01/19	Android/IOS game '	'Tra	aces" (DADIU). Role: Art Directi	on, Technical Art.		
EDUCATION						
9/2017-6/2019	Master Programme	e"V	isual Game and Media Design'	'- KADK, Copenhager	n	
9/2013-7/2017	Bachelor of Fine A	rts	– University of Seville			

TOOLS

Unity (from implementation to building)
Blender (3D, Animation)
Concepting (2D)
Adobe Suite
Shadergraph, VFX graph
C # programming (basic, prototyping)

PCG (Basic Houdini, Geo nodes in Blender)
Visual Programming (fast prototyping)
Commercial (marketing visuals)
Collaboration & Version Control (Git, Plastic)
Sound Design (trashy beats in Ableton)